黛安, 现在是早上6:42.
Diane, it's 6:42 a.m.
睡得不好.
Rough sleep.
我刚梦见自己在吃一颗,
大又无味的水果糖.
l had dreamt l was eating a large,
tasteless gumdrop.
我醒来后才发现
原来我在津津有味的大嚼
l awoke to realize
that l was aggressively munching
一粒放在枕头上的
硅胶耳塞.
on one of my Air-Pillow
silicone earplugs.
怪不得没有一点味道.
Hence the tastelessness.
大概晚餐后我应该
早点喝咖啡.
Perhaps l should keep a closer eye
on my after-dinner coffee consumption.
肋骨那里还是疼,
Persistent soreness in the rib area,
所以现在我每天早上
坚持练15分钟瑜伽.
which l'm treating each morning with
1 5 extra minutes of yogic discipline.
练完后, 谢天谢地,
疼痛终于撤退到我大脑
After which, thankfully,
the pain retreats to a cul-de-sac
意识不到的遥远的
神经死角了.
in a distant suburb
of my conscious mind.
今天的练习要开始了
倒立.
l'm going to begin today
with a headstand.
黛安, 我正头着地呢.
Diane, l am now upside down.
脑袋成了透气孔.
Mind becoming porous.
一天的任务都浮现在眼前.
目标越来越清晰可见.
The day's tasks coming into focus.
Objects growing clearer.
黛安, 巨人又对了.
我漏了东西.
Diane, the Giant was right.
l did forget something.
嘿. 还以为你在卡列斯佩尔森林
走丢了呢.
Hey. Thought we'd lost you
to the Kalispell woods.
2个退休女教师
住在帕尔默家旁边.
Two retired female schoolteachers
live in that house next to the Palmers.
她们对灰发男
一点印象都没有.
They have no memory
of a gray-haired man.
我喝了3壶甘菊茶
才查到的.
l had to drink three pots
of chamomile tea to find that out.
还提醒了我.
还是等一下再说吧?
Which reminds me.
Would you excuse me for a minute?
- 好的.
- 谢谢.
- Sure.
- Thanks.
继续找独臂人.
我们必须找到他.
Keep looking for the one-armed man.
We gotta find him.
打搅一下, 警长,
我想来和你道别
Excuse me, sheriff,
l just wanted to say goodbye
因为, 我告诉过你,
我要去塔科马港2天
because, as you know,
l'm going down to Tacoma for two days
去看我姐姐格温
和他丈夫拉利,
to visit my sister Gwen
and her husband, Larry,
他们上周生了个小孩.
who had a baby last week.
- 对.
- 就是, 格温有宝宝了.
- Right.
- That is, Gwen had the baby.
拉利做爸爸了.
你还记得他吗? 生了个男孩.
Larry's the father.
You remember? lt was a boy.
嗯, 反正, 那个来替班
的女孩很快就到了,
Well, anyway, as soon as
the Can-Do temp girl gets here,
我再交代一下,电话, 咖啡
还有对讲机都放在--
l'll explain the phones
and the coffee and the intercom--
- 露西, 没问题.
- 还有警车灯--
- Lucy, it's okay.
- And the wag--
我们会弄好的.
We got it covered.
不是, 她应该
马上就到了.
No, she should've
been here by now.
- 我可以等她,至少可以教教她--
- 露西, 别担心. 快走吧.
- l can stay and at least show her--
- Lucy, don't worry. Just go.
有时来替班的女生不知道的.
Sometimes the Can-Do girls can't.
- 但是, 警长--
- 我们会照顾好的.
- But, sheriff--
- We got it covered.
路上小心, 露西.
Have a safe trip, Lucy.
谢谢你.
Thank you.
- 早啊, 库.
- 哈里.
- Morning, Coop.
- Harry.
我们今晚要
放什么话出去?
What is the word
on our delivery tonight?
不需要了.
我们准备反扑他们吧.
We won't need it.
We've got the jump on them.
我知道欧蕊在哪儿了.
l know where Audrey is.
你看, 病人运送起重机
会帮助你顺利自如的移动
You see, the Port-O-Patient
will allow you to fluently transport
不幸的强生先生,
the unfortunate Mr. Johnson,
甚至可以在户外使用,
allowing him to even go outside,
让他坐着重新
感受大自然.
and sit and experience
what he can of nature.
平戈先生, 我想我表兄里欧
Mr. Pinkle, l want my cousin Leo
尽可能充分的
再次感受生命.
to have the fullest possible
experience of life.
对, 我就是为这个而来的.
好, 我们再来试试这个.
Well, that's what we're here for.
Okay, let's give it one more.
平戈先生,
你打算帮我安装滑道吗?
Mr. Pinkle,
are you gonna install the ramp?
好, 当然, 没问题, 没问题.
Well, sure, of course, of course.
事实上,
我早就准备好了--
As a matter of fact,
l already have some--
夹板做的滑道--
Some plywood ramp--
松木滑槽
我明天就帮你装. 一定.
Pinewood ramp boards
that l'll install tomorrow. Absolutely.
这个建议非常好.
现在, 我想我们可以来试试了.
That's a very good suggestion.
Now, l think we are ready to go.
最后. 来啦. 准备好了?
Finally. There we go. All right?
那儿有点小问题.
That's a new wrinkle.
真不敢相信. 它昨天还
运作的好好的.
l can't believe it. lt was working
just so perfectly yesterday.
动啊. 动啊--
Come on. Come on--
有时候就得对它粗暴点.
用力撞撞它.
You gotta be tough with this thing.
You gotta hit it hard.
就像对待女人一样, 在车间
我们常这样说. 快动啊.
A machine is like a woman, we always
say at the machine shop. Come on.
噢, 波比, 你没事吧?
Oh, Bobby, are you okay?
雪莉, 能给平戈先生
拿杯冷饮吗, 谢谢?
Shelly, could you get Mr. Pinkle
a cold drink, please?
麻烦我要健怡苏打.
有那个最好.
A diet soda, please.
That would be great.
平戈, 平戈, 平戈.
Pinkle, Pinkle, Pinkle.
这简直是个死亡陷阱.
我跟你说过我要他好好活着.
This thing is a death trap.
l told you we have to keep him alive.
保险公司是有进没出
他们不会全额赔偿的.
The insurance companies
don't exactly pay off like the slots.
拿了我们那份之后,
After we take our cuts,
剩下的就只够买这个
或者买个一流的独轮手推车.
we had only money for this
or a first-rate wheelbarrow.
噢, 太谢谢你了.
Oh, thank you very much.
哦, 非常感谢.
Oh, thanks a lot.
波比?
Bobby?
- 我要去见里欧的律师了.
- 听证会是今天, 对吧?
- l've gotta meet Leo's lawyer.
- The hearing's today, right?
再过一会儿就好了, 老友.
Be just another second, folks.
波比...
Bobby...
...我们能行吗?
...are we okay?
哇, 好了.
快来看看. 你看它.
Oh, that's it.
Come and take a look. You can see it.
运作的多顺畅.
lt works just fine.
跟我到外面.
Come outside with me.
让他自己弄去吧.
He can let himself out.
波比, 我们做的真棒.
好, 够了.
Bobby, we're doing real good.
Okay, that's enough.
波比?
Bobby?
波, 波, 我够不着开关.
波比, 我下不来了.
Bob, Bob, l can't reach the switch.
Bobby, l've got a problem here.
帕尔默先生
Mr. Palmer has pleaded not guilty
不承认
被指控为一级谋杀罪.
to the charge
of murder in the first degree.
并要求保释.
The defense has requested bail.
是否批准保释
将在审前听证会决定.
This pre-trial hearing is to determine
whether that bail will be granted.
检察官先生.
Mr. Prosecutor.
我们, 代表
华盛顿州的人民,
We, the people
of the State of Washington,
将驳回被告的保释请求.
move the defendant be denied bail.
其一,
On the basis of one,
他被指控
犯有极其严重的罪行.
the great seriousness of the crime
for which he has been accused.
其二, 这明显是
预谋的行为.
Two, the apparently
premeditated nature of this act.
第三, 证据表明
帕尔默先生
And three, the oft-witnessed
instability of Mr. Palmer
在他女儿死后
情绪一直极不稳定.
during the period
following the death of his daughter.
杜鲁门警长
为辩方发言.
Sheriff Truman will speak
for the defense.
法官大人,
Your Honor,
利兰·帕尔默
是我们社区里广为人知,
Leland Palmer
is a well-known, well-liked,
深受爱戴, 备受尊重
的一位成员.
well-respected member
of this community.
他的祖父.
His roots go way back.
约书亚·帕尔默, 带着家人,
His grandfather, Joshua Palmer,
来到这里落地生根
已有75年之久了.
brought the family here
more than 75 years ago.
法官大人, 没人能够
Your Honor, no one can know
切身体会利兰的
丧女之痛.
what it's like to lose a daughter
the way Leland did.
讲完了.
That's all.
谢谢你, 警长.
Thank you, sheriff.
罗威克先生, 你是否介意...?
Mr. Lodwick, would you care...?
我觉得这个
或许能在报纸上发表.
l thought l might sell this
to the Gazette.
他们好像挺喜欢
法庭素描的.
They seem to like
courtroom sketches.
对啊, 但你为什么不
把脸画明显些呢?
Yeah, why don't you try
for a little more face than that?
--考虑到他在本社区的崇高地位,
以及公众威望...
--high standing in the community,
and the pristine nature of his public...
个人看法而已.
Just an idea.
好. 谢了, 警长.
Good. Thanks, sheriff.
批准被告
保释外出.
The defendant is released
on his own recognizance.
现在, 利兰,
Now, Leland,
保释期间,
不得离开本镇
as you know,
l will require you to remain in town
并定期
向警长
and making your whereabouts
known to the sheriff
汇报行踪.
on a regular basis.
希, 查一下日历,
Sid, check the calendar,
我们会尽快
为帕尔默先生
and we'll set a date
for Mr. Palmer's trial
确定终审日期.
as soon as possible.
- 嗨.
- Hi.
谢谢你.
Thank you.
嗯, 这双深邃的蓝眼睛
今天在想些什么呢?
So, what's behind those
deep blue eyes today?
我有个提议.
l've got a proposition for you.
我想和你分享我的人生.
给你讲我的故事.
l'll share my life with you.
l'll tell it to you.
让它也成为你小说的一部分...
Part of your living novel...
...如果你让我看劳拉的日记.
...if you let me read Laura's diary.
好狡猾哦.
lt's intriguing.
我读给你听吧.
l'll read it to you.
但你听过的绝不能
流出这个房间.
But it mustn't physically
leave this room.
可以.
Acceptable.
- 现在开始吗?
- 当然.
- You'll start?
- Of course.
成交.
A bargain has been struck.
唐娜·海沃德.
Donna Hayward.
- 来吧.
- 好的.
- Begin.
- All right.
我来自双峰镇.
其实, 我出生在这里.
l'm from Twin Peaks.
Actually, l was born here.
我爸爸把我带到世上.
他是个医生.
My father delivered me.
He's a doctor.
那你从哪里来?
Where are you from?
我在波士顿长大的.
l grew up in Boston.
嗯, 实际上, 我是在书中长大的.
Well, actually, l grew up in books.
但有些事
你是无法从书中获得的.
There's things
you can't get in books.
从哪儿都
无法获得.
There are things
you can't get anywhere.
所以我们才寄望
能从他人身上获取.
But we dream
they can be found in other people.
继续吧.
Continue.
或许真能获得.
Maybe our dreams are real.
轮到我了.
My turn.
你干什么?
What are you doing?
可能,我会到屋外的
草坪去读.
Maybe l'll read it out here
on the lawn.
别玩了.
Please.
我们才开始啊.
We've only just started.
那你为什么不跟着我来.
Why don't you come with me?
来啊.
有什么好怕的?
Come on.
What's there to be afraid of?
快来啊.
Come on.
求你了?
Please?
把它还给我.
Give that back to me.
哈罗德?
Harold?
太对不起了.
l'm sorry.
请继续呈示
证据.
The defense will continue
with its evidence.
没问题吧, 拉辛先生.
lf you would, Mr. Racine.
你可以从脑电图看到,
You can see from these EEGs,
图表在这,
这是我的脑电波记录,
this chart here,
which is actually of my own head,
它显示了
正常的脑部活动.
is intended to show
normal brain activity.
我反对, 法官大人
不该使用 "正常" 这个字眼.
Objection to the use
of the word ''normal,'' Your Honor.
唔, 他解释的很准确.
Well, he's close enough.
反对无效.
Objection overruled.
强生先生的脑电图
则显示了极低微的活动状态.
This chart here is of Mr. Johnson
and shows minimal activity.
早前提交的
医学报告
A previously submitted
medical report
陈述的很清楚
强生先生的脑部已经严重损毁.
states that Mr. Johnson
has suffered diffuse brain damage.
目前,他甚至
还没能力接受
He doesn't currently
even have the perspicacity
最基本的
应激反应能力测试.
to take the standard CST
competency test.
因此我们认为
We therefore submit
在这种情况下再继续纠缠
that trying this individual
将会成为司法系统上
的一个莫大的笑柄.
would constitute a mockery
of the justice system.
在这个不幸的年轻人身上
继续诉讼程序
A proceeding that
the unfortunate young man
将不会有任何结果.
would not even faintly comprehend.
检察官先生.
Mr. Prosecutor.
我知道里欧·强生
现在的情况不是很好.
l know Leo Johnson
isn't in very good shape.
表面上, 坚持让他出庭
似乎有点荒谬.
On the surface, it might seem
ridiculous to make him stand trial.
但审讯不单是
惩罚坏人坏事.
But the trial does more
than just punish the wrongdoer.
更重要的是表达公义之声
并对社会起警示作用,杀鸡骇猴.
lt also brings a feeling of justice
and retribution to a community.
作为多起罪案的
嫌疑犯,
Among the various crimes
Leo Johnson is suspected of,
这类像劳拉·帕尔默的凶案
足以伤害到整个镇.
the murder of Laura Palmer is the sort
that can wound an entire town.
只要里欧·强生
还有一口气,
As long as Leo Johnson
carries a breath,
- 好了.
- 他就应出庭受审
- All right.
- he is as eminently deserving of a trial
这是整个社会
共有的意识和决心!
as this community is
of a sense of resolution!
够了.
All right.
现在, 请坐, 罗威克先生.
Now, have a seat, Mr. Lodwick.
好了, 各位
现在可以喘口气了.
Now, you fellas
can catch your breath.
我需要慎重审议.
l am going to need to deliberate.
库珀先生, 杜鲁门警长,
Mr. Cooper, Sheriff Truman,
希望你们能来
一同商议.
if l could have the pleasure
of your company.
希, 可以给我们来3杯
黑玉空乳乳调酒吗?
Sid, can you fix us up with three
black Yukon sucker punches?
是的, 法官大人.
Yes, Your Honor.
罗威克的立场很硬
盯得很紧.
Lodwick really planted his feet
and looked it in the eye.
没想到他对谋杀指控
那么执着.
l didn't expect him to press
on the murder charge.
库珀, 里欧·强生是我们的人吗?
Cooper, is Leo Johnson our man?
不, 先生. 我不认为他是.
No, sir. l don't believe he is.
哈里, 镇上的人
有什么想法?
Harry, what's the temperature
of the town?
他们是想公审还是处以私刑?
Do they want a trial or a lynching?
他们想要一个合适的人
把公义带来.
They want the right man
brought to justice.
那好, 看来他们不需要马戏团.
Well, they don't need a circus.
而这个小瘪三,
And this poor bastard,
看他也不过是颗愚妄的菜头罢了.
he seems to be a heady cabbage.
你觉得呢, 库珀?
Thoughts, Cooper?
我觉得
会抓到真凶的.
l feel the killer
will eventually be apprehended.
你得小心点.
他们都在打你的主意呢.
You have to watch these.
They sneak up on you.
我等一下就会宣布
l'm gonna declare Leo Johnson
里欧·强生不适宜出庭受审.
to be not competent to stand trial.
鉴于其病情,
他将被送返家中.
And when medically possible,
that he be shipped home.
哈里, 你想亲口
告诉那位小姐吗?
Harry, do you wanna tell
the little lady yourself?
谢谢, 克林顿.
Thanks, Clinton.
- 库珀, 你来着多久了?
- 12天了, 先生.
- Cooper, how long you been here?
- Twelve days, sir.
- 他们不打算起诉他了.
- 不起诉?
- They're not gonna try him.
- No?
里欧很快就可以回家了.
Leo is coming home.
我建议你密切留意
那些树林.
l'll advise you to keep your eye
on the woods.
这里的树林很神奇...
The woods are wondrous here...
...也奇怪.
...but strange.
谢谢.
Thanks.
有什么行李要我拿吗, 纳丁?
Can l get you anything, Nadine?
- 你是谁?
- 我是谁?
- Who are you?
- Who am l?
- 你也上高中吗.
- 对, 是的.
- You go to the high school.
- Well, yeah.
啊, 我一下子没想起来.
因为你不是我同班.
Yeah, it took me a second.
You're not in any of my classes.
去坐着吧, 甜心.
我给你拿饮料.
Why don't you sit down, honey?
Let me get you a drink.
噢, 不用, 我自己拿.
Oh, no, l'll get it.
爸和妈呢?
Where are Mom and Dad?
哦, 出镇去了.
Oh, out of town.
那好.
Okay.
You're a jack and I'm a jack
And SteepIejacks are we
海沃德医生说
是后遗症.
Doc Hayward said
to roll with the punches.
你打算带她去
杰柯比医生那儿吗?
Have you thought about maybe
taking her to see Dr. Jacoby?
不, 他现在夏威夷
疗养心脏病呢.
No, he's in Hawaii
recovering from that heart attack.
它就这样掉下来了.
lt just came right off.
- 托吉麻辣先生要见你
- 什么先生?
- Mr. Tojamura is here.
- Mister who?
不好意思.
Excuse me.
- 你有预约吗, 怎么称呼...?
- 托吉麻辣.
- Do you have an appointment, Mr...?
- Tojamura.
我代表亚洲投资银行.
l represent Asian investment bank.
出高价
We have superior offer
购买格斯伍计划.
for Ghostwood Project.
我有东京银行
的委托信
l have commitment letters
from Tokyo banks
准备马上启动计划.
prepared to move immediately.
这些听来都非常有趣,
This all sounds very interesting,
但真不凑巧, 我马上有一个
重要的电话会议要开.
but unfortunately, l have an important
conference call in a couple of minutes.
我有计划书...
l have prospectus...
- 或许改天吧.
- ...和诱人的.
- Perhaps some other time.
- ...and taste.
五.
Five.
百万?
Million?
我想你把这个留下.
好让我们的人都看看.
l would like you to leave these.
Let my people have a look at them.
正中下怀.
Point of visit.
谢谢, 托吉麻辣先生.
库珀就到了.
Cooper's on his way.
加拿大的电话, 荷恩先生.
Your caII from Canada, Mr. Horne.
- 绑匪的电话?
- 是.
- ls that our call?
- Yes.
你来的正是时候.
You pushed it pretty close.
- 本杰明·荷恩.
- 钱准备好了么?
- Benjamin Horne.
- Are you ready to pIay?
欧蕊.
Audrey.
- 我要和我女儿讲话.
- 等今晚吧.
- l wanna talk to my daughter.
- That can wait for tonight.
一次. 越过边境,
One time. Across the border,
离东大福克斯五米,
去卡斯尔加市的那条路,
five miIes east of Grand Forks,
on the road to CastIegar,
有一家哥伦比亚酒吧.
is a bar caIIed the CoIumbian.
后面
是一个废弃的游乐场.
Behind it
is a faiIed amusement park.
找到旋转木马.
Go to the merry-go-round.
在一匹无头马旁
放下公文箱,
Leave the briefcase
beside the horse with no head,
午夜, 一个人.
at midnight, aIone.
我会派人去的.
l'll be sending my representative.
按你的指示,
全是连号钞.
Serialized denominations,
as you instructed.
我女儿的命就交给你了.
My daughter's life is in your hands.
电话联系.
Stay by a phone.
跟踪他.
Follow him.
确保他和钱
都要安全到达.
Make sure that he and the money
are neatly delivered.
- 把欧蕊带回来.
- 不是库珀带她回来吗?
- Bring Audrey back.
- Cooper's not bringing her back?
库珀回不来了.
Cooper isn't coming back.
如果你能应付得了,
lf you can manage it,
把欧蕊和钱箱
都带回来.
bring back Audrey
and the briefcase.
5百万美金.
Five million dollars.
好啊, 真是个丰收日啊.
Now, that's a good day's work.
好,
你进了哈罗德的公寓,
All right,
once you're in Harold's apartment,
动作要快.
move as fast as you can.
好紧张哦.
This is scary.
劳拉的日记就在左边书柜
最下面的一个暗格里,
Laura's diary is in a secret shelf
at the very bottom of the bookcase,
藏在一排假书后面.
behind a row of fake books.
嗯, 我想暗格的开关
就在书柜右边
Now, l think that there's a doohickey
on the right-hand side
不知怎么地
就可以让暗格打开.
that somehow lets the shelf
slide out and down.
所有书都是一个样的,
除了劳拉那本.
All the notebooks look the same,
except for Laura's.
红色封面的小本本.
Hers is smaller with a red cover.
你打算怎么把他
带到屋外?
How are you gonna get him
to go outside?
不去屋外,
只是离开客厅.
Not outside,
just out of the front room.
我会在窗口
用手电给你打信号.
Then l'll signal you with the flashlight
through the window.
门会开着的.
The door will be open.
我还以为你喜欢这个人.
l thought you liked this guy.
没错.
l do.
可以了.
Okay.
库珀递钱箱给我.
Cooper hands me the briefcase.
我一拿就...
l take it...
那本·荷恩呢?
What about Ben Horne?
他嘛, 就放弃
赌场的控制权.
Well, he give up control
of One-Eyed Jack's.
你接管.
lt's yours.
把他女儿干掉?
With his daughter dead?
你啊, 爱吃牛排
You know, you love a good steak
却不知道怎样把牛排
弄到自己的碟里.
but you don't want to know
how it got on your plate.
你必须要学会
怎样做交易, 布莱奇.
You must be serious about
your business, Blackie.
那你打算怎么处置她?
How are you gonna do the girl?
就用这个处置啊
Voila.
- 她睡了?
- 可香了.
- Does the girl sleep?
- Dreamland.
来, 来, 来. 过来我这儿.
Come, come, come. Come to me.
那个女孩在另一房间,
梦见鱼儿们
ln the other room,
the girl dreams of fishes
在黑暗湖底的乱水草里
游来游去.
and dark lakebeds
and tangle weeds.
怎么处理布莱奇?
What about Blackie?
- 我已经等够了.
- 我们今晚来爽爽吧.
- l've waited long enough.
- We have our fun tonight.
吻我.
Kiss me.
是. 好的. 再见.
Right. Okay. Bye.
- 实验室辅助热线.
- 噢, 我想查询检验结果.
- Laboratory Services.
- Yeah, l'm calling for some test results.
海沃德医生说
直接打给你就行了--
Doc Hayward said
l could just call you up and--
- 是的, 请问哪个项目呢, 先生?
- 哪个项目?
- Yes, what test was it for, sir?
- What's it for?
是的, 请告诉我, 先生.
Yes, pIease, sir.
是精液透析.
姓'布伦南', 名'安迪'.
lt was for a semen's analysis.
Brennan, Andy.
- 抱歉, 我听不清楚, 先生.
- 哦. 布伦南, 安迪.
- I'm sorry, I can't hear you, sir.
- Sorry. Brennan, Andy.
哦, 透析结果是
精液缺失, 先生.
Oh, the doctor's anaIysis
is oIigospermia, sir.
是, 你能说慢点吗.
我想写下来.
Yes, could you go slower.
l wanna write all this down.
- 精液缺失.
- "精液缺失."
- OIigospermia.
- ''Oligospermia.''
- 是的.
- 那太可怕了.
- That's right.
- That sounds terrible.
- 我得了那个?
- 不, 先生. 是之前.
- l have that?
- No, sir. You had that.
哦, 之前.
Oh, l had it.
- It means too few sperms.
- ''Too few sperms.''
- 精虫很少.
- "精虫很少."
但它们的情况很好, 先生.
Very good, sir.
你是说我好了?
You mean l'm cured?
医生说
它们不但能造人--
The doctor says
they're not just three men on a--
"医生说
它们不但能造人,
''Doc says they're not just
three men on a fishing trip,
- 而且能造一个镇的人.
- 而且能造一个镇的人."
- They're a whoIe damn town.
- they're a whole damn town.''
- 是的, 先生. 你理解了吗?
- 嗯, 我理解.
- That's right, sir. Do you understand?
- Yeah, l know what it means.
就是说它们还不是真人
但, 它们能够--
lt means they're not really real
people, they're--
- 抱歉, 先生, 我要接其他来电了.
- 哦, 好的. 谢谢你.
- I'm sorry, sir, I've got another caII.
- Oh, okay. Thank you.
- 不客气, 先生.
- 非常感谢你.
- You're weIcome, sir.
- Thank you very much.
我能造一个镇的人!
l'm a whole damn town!
我能造一个镇的人.
l'm a whole damn town.
别问了.
Don't ask.
我们刚说到哪儿了?
Where were we?
好, 吧台
和接待室在这里.
Okay, main bar
and greeting room here.
那边是赌场和贵宾室.
Casino and get-acquainted room.
- 这个呢, 布莱奇的办公室?
- 我们到了就会知道.
- What's this, Blackie's office?
- We'll find out when we get there.
独臂人在9号公路的
'知更鸟巢'汽车旅馆呆过.
The one-armed man is staying in
the Robin's Nest Motel on Highway 9.
至少一天,或一天半
没人见过他了.
Nobody's seen him for at least
a day, a day and a half.
房间有住过的痕迹.
The room looks lived-in.
我找到这个.
l found this.
和上次的药一样.
Same drug as last time.
有奇异味道, 很重 .
A weird, deep smell.
我们还在等艾伯特的分析报告.
干得好, 豪克.
We're still waiting on Albert's analysis.
Good work, Hawk.
豪克, 明早见.
Hawk, see you in the morning.
继续.
Okay.
我们穿过树林
到后门去.
We'll approach through the woods
to the rear door.
里面的楼梯一直
通往工作间.
lnside are stairs leading down
to the working rooms.
我估计,
欧蕊就在那里.
My guess is,
that's where Audrey's being held.
有几个打手在那儿?
What kind of muscle do they have?
赌场前门有2个看守,
后门可能更多.
A couple of floor men in the casino,
probably more in the back.
我们出发吧.
Let's go get her.
- 晚安, 安迪.
- 明早见, 安迪.
- Good night, Andy.
- See you in the morning, Andy.
今天辛苦了.
Good work.
"格温和莱利."
''Gwen and Larry.''
- 亚当人流诊所.
- 唯, 露西在吗--? 什么?
- Adam's Abortion CIinic.
- Hi, is Lucy--? What?
亚当人流诊所.
Adam's Abortion CIinic.
嗷, 我的天啊.
Oh, my God.
能打包一杯咖啡吗?
Can l get a cup of coffee to go?
- 嗨.
- Hi.
麻烦你, 大杯.
Large, please.
- 你今天见过唐娜?
- 没, 抱歉.
- So you seen Donna today?
- No, sorry.
- 你呢?
- 也没.
- You?
- No.
- 那, 买咖啡给谁?
- 咖啡?
- So, what's with the coffee?
- Coffee?
给利兰叔叔的.
lt's for Uncle Leland.
家里没咖啡了吗?
You don't have coffee at home?
詹姆斯, 我没时间聊了.
James, l can't talk now.
- 要走了.
- 你要走了?
- l need to go.
- You need to go?
- 去哪儿?
- 回家. 再见, 詹姆斯.
- Where are you going?
- Home. Bye, James.
唐娜·海沃德.
Donna Hayward.
3月7日, 周二.
第二节.
March 7th, Tuesday.
Second session.
亲爱的日记...
Dear diary...
今天讲很久之前的事.
好吗?
This is from a long time ago.
ls that okay?
我那时大约13岁, 可能14了.
l was about 1 3 years old, 1 4 maybe.
我和劳拉穿上最紧,
最短的裙子. 紧的穿不进.
Me and Laura put on our tightest,
shortest skirts. Too tight.
但劳拉硬帮我穿上了.
But Laura talked me into it.
我们去公路旅馆酒吧
和男生约会.
We were going to the Roadhouse
to meet boys.
他们叫
Their names are
乔希, 瑞克,还有提姆.
Josh, Rick and Tim.
他们20来岁.
They're about 20 years old.
对我们不错.
And they're nice to us.
让我们觉得
自己长大了点.
And they make us feel
like we're older.
瑞克问我要不要去舞会.
Rick asks if we wanna go party.
然后劳拉说, 去.
And Laura says, yes.
那一刻, 我有点
迟疑了.
And all of a sudden, l feel this knot
building up in my stomach.
但劳拉已经和瑞克上车了
我无论如何也得去.
But when Laura gets in the truck
with Rick, l go anyway.
树林在涌动.
Stream in the woods.
满月, 我记得.
Full moon, l think.
又白又亮.
lt's pale and light out.
劳拉开始围着那些男生
跳起舞来.
Laura starts to dance
around the boys.
她开始扭动腰肢...
She begins to move her hips...
...来来回回.
...back and forth.
瑞克开始拍手, 但提姆没有
他只是看着.
Rick starts to clap, but Tim doesn't
do anything, he just watches.
不知怎的, 我觉得很恼怒.
Somehow, that makes me angry.
于是我说, "我们去裸泳吧."
So l say, ''Let's go skinny-dipping.''
我们脱光了衣服.
We take off our clothes.
我知道那些男生在看着.
l know the boys are watching.
劳拉开始和乔希,瑞克接吻.
Laura starts to kiss Josh and Rick.
而我却不知所措.
l don't know what to do.
所以我游开了.
So l swim away.
我觉得自己想逃离, 但我没有.
l feel like l wanna run, but l don't.
这时,提姆游了过来.
Tim swims out to me.
他先吻了我的手...
He kisses my hand...
...接着吻唇.
...and then me.
那感觉至今还在.
l can still feel that kiss.
他的双唇又暖又甜.
His lips are warm and sweet.
我的心猛跳.
My heart jumps.
他说什么,
我都听不清了.
He's talking to me,
but l can't hear him.
只有吻.
Only the kiss.
后来再也没见过他了.
l never saw him again.
那就是我的初恋.
lt was the first time l ever fell in love.
就这些了.
That's all.
太美了, 唐娜.
That was beautiful, Donna.
我来对付他.
l got him.
哈里.
Harry.
在这等, 哈里.
Wait here, Harry.
不通. 死路.
No. Dead end.
- 2个人.
- 欧蕊呢?
- Two.
- Audrey?
仔细想想,
还不赖嘛.
Not such a bad way to go,
all things considered.
不赖, 不赖. 计划完美.
No, no. lt's beautiful.
- 她一个人?
- 南希在.
- ls she alone?
- Nancy's with her.
有什么是她能为你做而我不能?
What does she do for you l can't?
嗯, 新鲜感.
Well, something new.
很多人以为兰花要生长在
国外潮湿的地方.
Most people imagine orchids
growing in exotic, steamy places.
其实哪里都可以种.
But you can grow them anywhere.
主要是水分
和阳光, 不是吗?
lt's all basically a matter
of water and light, isn't it?
真美.
lt's beautiful.
这儿, 看.
Here, look.
明白吗, 湿度最重要.
嗯, 我是说, 是湿度的控制.
See, humidity is paramount.
Well, the control of it, l mean.
太湿
容易病.
Too much moisture
is an invitation to disease.
3个萼片和3个花瓣.
Three sepals and three petals.
底部的花瓣,
因为长得像下唇,
The bottom petal,
shaped like a lower lip,
所以叫唇瓣.
is called a labellum.
好精致.
So delicate.
嗯, 其实是个月台,
真的, 为了让昆虫降落授粉.
Well, it's the landing platform,
really, for pollinating insects.
真浪漫, 是吧?
Romantic, isn't it?
恕我失陪一会儿?
Will you excuse me a minute?
你好.
Hi.
可以带我去见
欧蕊·荷恩, 劳驾了?
Would you take me
to Audrey Horne, please?
- 她不在.
- 那我们再去看看吧.
- l don't think she's available.
- Let's double-check.
这可不是我的主意, 好吗?
lt's not my idea, okay?
对他们
你只是砧板上的一块肉.
You're nothing but meat on a hook
to these people.
闭嘴.
Shut up.
欧蕊, 能听见我吗?
Audrey, can you hear me?
我的祈祷.
My prayers.
欧蕊, 我现在要
带你离开这里了.
Audrey, l'm gonna take you
out of here now.
别.
No.
和我吻别.
When you leave me with a kiss.
你还是老样子,
很好.
That's the way you want it,
that's fine.
把枪放下.
Drop the gun.
慢点放.
Slowly.
现在, 转过身去.
Now, turn around.
幸好你们
藏不住秘密.
Good thing you guys
can't keep a secret.
投得好.
Good throw.
发生了枪战.
There's been gunfire.
杜鲁门和库珀
带着你女儿走了.
Truman and Cooper are leaving
with your daughter.
看看, 你是谁?
Now, who can this be?
罗威克先生. 检察官办事处, 嗯?
Monsieur Lodwick. DA's office, eh?
- 怎么了?
- 没事.
- ls something wrong?
- No.
你吓了我一大跳, 这样而已.
You just frightened me, that's all.
来这边.
Come here.
给我讲讲这个兰花. 这棵.
Tell me about this orchid. This one.
哈罗德, 不, 你不明白.
Harold, no, you don't understand.
马蒂!
Maddy!
等等!
Wait!
你们在找秘密吗?
Are you looking for secrets?
全都只是为了那个吗?
ls that what all this is about?
好, 或许我能帮助你们.
Well, maybe l can help you.
你们想知道
终极秘密是什么吗?
Do you know
what the ultimate secret is?
你们想知道吗
You want to know?
劳拉知道.
Laura did.
知道是谁杀了你.
The secret of knowing who killed you.